Finding Aid for Yale Kamisar Papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Research Topical Files, 2003-2004; 14. 4 linear feet
  - R-S
    - San Jose Mercury News, undated (Box 12)
    - Santa Barbara, California Workshop for Judges for 9th Circuit, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
    - Sapala, Michael F., 1985 (Box 12)
    - Saunders, Kevin W., 1984-1987 (Box 12)
    - Scalia, Antonin, 1986-1992 (Box 13)
    - Schaefer, Walter, 1980-1983 (Box 13)
    - Schairer, Jack E., 1981 (Box 13)
    - Schauer, Fred F., 1990-1991 (Box 13)
    - Schneider, Carl, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
    - Schrock, Tom, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
    - Schulhofer, Stephen, 1981-1992 (Box 13)
    - Schwab, Stewart, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Schwartz, Herman, 1982-1998 (Box 13)
    - Schwartz, Louis B., 1983 (Box 13)
    - School Searches, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - Scott, George M., 1959 (Box 13)
    - Search and Seizure, 1981-1994; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Searches, Aerial, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Seat Belts, undated (Box 13)
    - Sedler, Robert A., 1983; 1993 (Box 13)
    - Seeburger, Richard, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Seidman, Louis Michael, 1982; 1992 (Box 13)
    - Seminar Supplement Material, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Senate Judiciary Committee, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Separation of Powers, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Serritella, Joseph J., 1989 (Box 13)
    - Sessions, Judge, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Seton Hall Law School, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Shapiro, E. Donald, 1984-1996 (Box 13)
    - Shapiro, Harold, 1982-1986 (Box 13)
    - Shellow, Jim, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Shiffrin, Steven, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Shopping (for Judges), 1987 (Box 13)
    - Shudofsky, Alisa, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Siebert, Sharon, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Siegan, B.H., 1988 (Box 13)
    - Silver, Edward S., 1959-1960 (Box 13)
    - Silvergate, Harvey, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Silverstein, Lee, 1963-1964 (Box 13)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Simon, Rita, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Simons, Kenneth, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Simpson, Brian A.W., 1983 (Box 13)
    - Singer, Shelley, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Singer Brothers (Old), 1982 (Box 13)
    - Sixth Circuit, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Skolnick, Jerome, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Skorneck, Carolyn, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Sloan, Ayana, 1986 (Box 13)
    - Slote, Hetzie, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Smith, William F., 1982 (Box 13)
    - Smoking, 1987 (Box 13)
    - SMU (Southern Methodist University), 1990 (Box 13)
    - Snepp, Frank, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Snow, Frederick M., 1985 (Box 13)
    - Souter, David, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Southern Prisoner's Defense Committee, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Sovern, Michael I., 1958 (Box 13)
    - Sowle, Claude R., 1962 (Box 13)
    - Spaeth, Harold Joseph, 1980-1993 (Box 13)
    - Sparks, Pat, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Special Prosecutors, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Sperling, Gene, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - St. Antoine, Theodore, 1977; 1987 (Box 13)
    - St. John's University, undated (Box 13)
    - St. Whitelock, Otto, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Stacy, Tom, 1983-1993 (Box 13)
    - Stanford Daily, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Starr, Ken, 1989 (Box 13)
    - State Bar of Michigan, 1993; undated (Box 13)
    - States Rights, 1986-1992 (Box 13)
    - Stein, Robert A., 1984-1992 (Box 13)
    - Stephenson, Donald Grier, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Stern, Herbert, 1983-1988 (Box 13)
    - Stevens, John Paul, 1982-1991 (Box 13)
    - Stewart, Potter, 1981-1985 (Box 13)
    - Stillwagon, Allan, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Stone, Geoffrey R., 1989-1991 (Box 13)
    - Streib, Victor L., 1985-1988 (Box 13)
    - Student Interviews, 1978 (Box 13)
    - Student Lawyer, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Stuntz, William, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Suicide
      - Assisted, 1993 (Box 13)
      - Bouvia, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Suicide Bill, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Sukenik, John, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Sullivan, Kathleen, 1986-1990 (Box 13)
    - Sum and Substance, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
    - Supreme Court (U.S.)
      - 1971 (Box 13)
      - 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - 1988 (Box 13)
      - Historical Society, 1997 (Box 13)
      - Jurisdiction, 1981 (Box 13)
      - Library, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Survey Research Center, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Swartz, Stephen B., undated (Box 13)
    - Syverud, Kent, 1982-1992 (Box 13)
  - T-Z
    - Tarlow, Barry, 1986-1994 (Box 13)
    - Task Force on Violent Crime, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Taxes, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Lydia C., 1985 (Box 13)
    - Teaching
      - 1977-1978 (Box 13)
      - Inquiries, 1974-1978 (Box 13)
      - Techniques, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Television Shows
      - "Brooklyn Bridge,", 1991-1992 (Box 13)
      - Transcripts, 1963-1987 (Box 13)
    - Temko, Stanley L., 1957 (Box 14)
    - Tennis, 1973-1983 (Box 14)
    - Tenure Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 14)
    - Tenure Procedure, 1990; undated (Box 14)
    - Texas Lawyer, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Theft, undated (Box 14)
    - Thiede, Brian E., 1985 (Box 14)
    - Third Circuit Judicial Conference, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Thomas, George, 1996-1997 (Box 14)
    - Thompson, James R., 1964 (Box 14)
    - Thompson, Richard, 1991-1996 (Box 14)
    - Time Magazine, 1977-1993 (Box 14)
    - "The Today Show,", 1991 (Box 14)
    - Toledo Blade, 1990; undated (Box 14)
    - Tollett, Kenneth, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Torricelli, Paul, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Trakman, Leon E., 1991 (Box 14)
    - Traynor, Roger J., 1961-1963 (Box 14)
    - Trial Magazine, 1991-1998 (Box 14)
    - Trial Movies, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Tribe, Laurence, 1991-1995 (Box 14)
    - Trott, Stephen, 1991-1993 (Box 14)
    - Tulsa, University of, College of Law, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
    - Turner Geriatric Services, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Undergraduate
      - Criminal Procedure, 1973 (Box 14)
      - Undergraduate Law Teaching, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Universities, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Urban, Otto, includes photograph, 1962-1963 (Box 14)
    - U.S. Law Week
      - 1981-1988, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Utley, Robert L., 1981 (Box 14)
    - Uvillier, Richard H., 1985 (Box 14)
    - Van Alstyne, William, 1986-1992 (Box 14)
    - Van Norden, Montagnie, Jr., 1989 (Box 14)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1984-1991 (Box 14)
    - Vaughn, Shelby J., 1993 (Box 14)
    - Velleman, David, 1991-1994 (Box 14)
    - Vernon, David H., 1983 (Box 14)
    - Vining, Joe, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Violent Crime, undated (Box 14)
    - Virginia Trial Lawyers Association, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Vita, includes photographs, 1998-2004 (Box 14)
    - Vitiello, Michael, 1984-1994 (Box 14)
    - Voice of America, 1981 (Box 14)
    - Voting Rights, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Wachtler, Sol, 1985-1997 (Box 14)
    - Waggoner, L.W., 1988 (Box 14)
    - Wald, Pat, 1988-1990 (Box 14)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1979-1994 (Box 14)
    - Warren, Earl, 1969; 1987 (Box 14)
    - Warren, Gorham & Lamont, 1979-1989 (Box 14)
    - Washington Post, 1981-2000 (Box 14)
    - Washington Times, 1983-1988 (Box 14)
    - Wasserstrom, Silas, 1982 (Box 14)
    - Watson, Andrew, 1989-1997 (Box 14)
    - Weapons Search, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Weber Case, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Wechsler Article, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Wechsler, Herbert, 1959-1991 (Box 14)
    - Weinreb, Lloyd L., 1982-1985 (Box 14)
    - Weinstein, Jack B., 1963-1994 (Box 14)
    - Weintraub, Barbara, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Weisbard, Alan J., 1993 (Box 14)
    - Weisberg, Bernard, 1963-1986 (Box 14)
    - Weisberg, Jack, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Weisberg, Robert, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Weisberger, Joseph, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Weisselberg, Charles, 1998 (Box 14)
    - Werder, Rick, 1982-1984 (Box 14)
    - Westen, Peter, 1978-1990 (Box 14)
    - Whitaker, Gilbert, 1990 (Box 14)
    - White, Alexandra, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
    - White, Byron, 1984-1993 (Box 14)
    - White, James B., 1963-1984 (Box 14)
    - White, James J., 1987 (Box 14)
    - White, Margot, 1998 (Box 14)
    - White, Tricia, 1988-1992 (Box 14)
    - White, Welsh, 1966-1989; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Whitmore Case, 1988 (Box 14)
    - Wiener, Frederick Bernays, 1959-1960 (Box 14)
    - Wilkes, Donald E., 1982-1990 (Box 14)
    - Wilkey/Kamisar Debate, 1979-1982 (Box 15)
    - Wilkey, Malcolm Richard, 1983; undated (Box 15)
    - Wilkinson, J. Harvie, III, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Will, George, 1983-1991 (Box 15)
    - William and Mary, College of
      - Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 15)
      - Examinations, 1988; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Williams, Alexander, 1990-1996 (Box 15)
    - Williams, David, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Williams, E.B., 1988 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Glanville, 1988-1999 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Harrison, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Williams, Warren F., 1955-1957 (Box 15)
    - Williams, William L., 1994-1997 (Box 15)
    - Wills, 1988 (Box 15)
    - Wilson, Bradford, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Wojcik, Paul, 1982-1984 (Box 15)
    - Wolf, Susan, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Wollin, David, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Wolson, Craig, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Wright, Charles Alan, 1984-1997 (Box 15)
    - Wright, J. Skelly, 1963 (Box 15)
    - Writing, 1993 (Box 15)
    - WTVS/Channel 56, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Wu, Frank, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Wyoming, 1982-1986 (Box 15)
    - Yackle, Larry W., 1990 (Box 15)
    - Yale Law Journal, 1989-1993 (Box 15)
    - Yale University, 1978-2001 (Box 15)
    - Yeager, Daniel, 1990 (Box 15)
    - Young, Richard, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Yudof, Mark G., 1982-1987 (Box 15)
    - Zengerle, Joseph C., 1983-1986 (Box 15)
    - Zimring, Franklin E., undated (Box 15)
    - Zion, Sidney, 1979-1994 (Box 15)
- Research Topical Files, 1962-1981
  (2012 Accession)
  - A-E
    - AALS Committee on Readings in Criminal Law, 1964 (Box 25)
    - AALS Special Committee on Supreme Court Decisions, 1964-1966; 3 folders (Box 25)
    - ACLU Shoot to Kill, 1967-1968 (Box 25)
    - Chelsea House, 1967-1968 (Box 25)
    - Cheatham, Elliott E., 1965-1966 (Box 25)
    - Chenoweth, Priscilla Read Rutgers (The State University), 1967-1968 (Box 25)
    - Childress, Bill, 1968 (Box 25)
    - Choper, Jesse (Prof.), 1970-1974 (Box 25)
    - Christopher, Warren, 1968 (Box 25)
    - Cipes, Robert M., 1968 (Box 25)
    - Clark, Leroy D., 1975-1976 (Box 25)
    - Clark, Ramsey, 1965; 1967 (Box 25)
    - Clark, Thomas (Ret. Justice), 1968 (Box 25)
    - Cleary, Edward W. (Prof.), 1969 (Box 25)
    - Cleary, John J. (Nat'l Defender), 1966 (Box 25)
    - Clinton Street Bar, 1967 (Box 25)
    - Coates, James D. (West Publishing), 1979-1980 (Box 25)
    - Coffin, Frank, 1976-1977 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Alan N., 1968 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Avern, 1965-1966 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Carl (Prof.), 1969 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Donald S., 1979 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Fred, 1965; 1969-1972; 1974-1975 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Herbert B. (Justice, Pa.) (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Jerome A., 1966 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, Meredith J., 1971 (Box 25)
    - Cohen, William B., 1967 (Box 25)
    - Cohn, Sherman L. (Prof.), 1968 (Box 25)
    - Colburn, C. William (Debator), 1965 (Box 25)
    - Cole, George F., 1973 (Box 25)
    - Coleman, Mary S., 1979 (Box 25)
    - Coltin, Wendell H., 1960 (Box 25)
    - Columbia Law School, 1968 (Box 25)
    - Conrad, Larry A., 1966-1967 (Box 25)
    - Cook Budget, 1970 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Dershowitz, Alan M., 1965 (Box 25)
    - Desmond, John (New York Times Magazine), 1969-1970 (Box 25)
    - Detroit Free Press, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Dixon, Robert G., Jr., 1966-1967 (Box 25)
    - Dobris, Joel C., 1965 (Box 25)
    - Dodge, John F., 1966 (Box 25)
    - Dodyk, Paul (Box 25)
    - Donahue, Charles, 1967-1968; 1977 (Box 25)
    - Donnici, Peter J., 1972 (Box 25)
    - Dorsen, Norman, 1965; 1970 (Box 25)
    - Douglas, Randolph L. (C.J. Barbados Supreme Court), 1967 (Box 25)
    - Douglas, William O. (Supreme Court Justice), 1972 (Box 25)
    - Downing, A.B., 1970 (Box 25)
    - Doyle, James E. (Judge), 1977 (Box 25)
    - Drinnan, Robert F. (Dean), 1969 (Box 25)
    - DuBois, Elizabeth Bartholet (Student), 1967 (Box 25)
    - DuBois, W.E. Burghardt (Box 25)
    - Ducat, Craig R. (Northern Illinois University), 1970 (Box 25)
    - Duke, Steve (Yale Law School), 1970; 1973 (Box 25)
    - Dykhouse, David, 1969 (Box 25)
    - Eagan, Emmett E., 1972 (Box 25)
  - H-L
    - Haines, Andrew, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Hale, James, 1965 (Box 26)
    - Hall, Livingston, 1965-1966; 1975; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Halpern, Jeanne, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Hambly, A.D., 1965 (Box 26)
    - Hammer (New York Times) (Box 26)
    - Hard, William (Reader's Digest), 1964 (Box 26)
    - Harper's, 1969 (Box 26)
    - Harris, Richard, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Harris, Robert J. (UM Law School), 1967; 1969 (Box 26)
    - Harris, William (Bench Bar Conference), 1969 (Box 26)
    - Hart, Philip A., 1970-1971; 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Harvard Law Review, 1968-1969 (Box 26)
    - Hastie, William (Judge), 1965 (Box 26)
    - Hathaway, John, 1973; 1980 (Box 26)
    - Haynsworth, Clement F., Jr., 1966; 1968-1969; 1975; 1978-1979 (Box 26)
    - Hays, Paul R. (Judge), 1965; 1972 (Box 26)
    - Hazard, Geoffrey C., Jr., 1965; 1980 (Box 26)
    - Healy, Patrick F. (Nat'l District Attorney), 1967 (Box 26)
    - Herbert, Norman, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Herman, Lawrence (Prof.), 1964-1965; 1968 (Box 26)
    - Herzstein, Robert E., 1980 (Box 26)
    - Hess, Albert G. (Int'l Crm'l Law), 1966 (Box 26)
    - Higgenbotham, A. Leon, Jr., 1979 (Box 26)
    - High School Debate Assembly, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Highway Safety, 1964-1966 (Box 26)
    - Hill, Alfred, 1976 (Box 26)
    - Hiss, Donald (Covington and Burling), 1967 (Box 26)
    - Hodson, Kenneth J. (Judge Advocate), 1968
    - Hoezel, William (Judicature), 1978-1980 (Box 26)
    - Hoffa, James R., 1971 (Box 26)
    - Hogan, William E., 1966; 1968 (Box 26)
    - Hoggett, John (Prof.), 1967 (Box 26)
    - Hollister, David C. (Rep.), 1978-1980 (Box 26)
    - Holper, Victor J., 1969 (Box 26)
    - Hoobler, Sibley (UM Medical Center), 1969 (Box 26)
    - Hooker, Evelyn (Prof.), 1969 (Box 26)
    - L.K. & C. Constitutional Law (Box 26)
    - Law Quad Notes, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Lawyer's Literary Club, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Lebedeff, Diane, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Lee, Riva, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Lee, Stephen E., 1967 (Box 26)
    - Lee, Wonno (Information Services), 1969 (Box 26)
    - Leech, Noyes, 1976 (Box 26)
    - Lehman, Warren (Prof.), 1966-1967 (Box 26)
    - Leibowitz, Arnold H., 1966 (Box 26)
    - Leighton, George N. (Judge), 1966 (Box 26)
    - Leiser, Burton M., 1979-1980 (Box 26)
    - Leitman, Bruce, 1967; 1971; 1976 (Box 26)
    - Lempert, Richard (Prof.), 1971 (Box 26)
    - Lent, Berkeley (Justice), 1979 (Box 26)
    - Lesar, Hiram H., 1967 (Box 26)
    - Lesser, Stanley C., 1964-1967; 1971; 1973 (Box 26)
    - Leventhal, Harold, 1966-1969; 1972 (Box 26)
    - Levi, Edward, 1973; 1975 (Box 26)
    - Levien, Michael (Peter Owen Ltd.), 1969 (Box 26)
    - Levin, A. Leo, 1965 (Box 26)
    - Levin, Carl, 1979 (Box 26)
    - Levin, Charles L. (Court of Appeals), 1970-1972; 1974-1977; 1980 (Box 26)
    - Levin, Gerald S. (Judge), 1967 (Box 26)
    - Levine, Alan H. (ACLU), 1966 (Box 26)
    - Levy, Robert J., (Prof.), 1967 (Box 26)
    - Lewin, Fred (Asst. Dean), 1965 (Box 26)
    - Lewis, David, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Lewis, Peter W., 1980 (Box 26)
    - Lewis, Robert, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Lewis, Thomas P. (Prof.), 1964-1965 (Box 26)
    - Library (Law School), 1967 (Box 26)
    - Lichten, Thomas R., 1972 (Box 26)
    - Lieberman, Daniel L., 1966; 1972 (Box 26)
    - Life Magazine (Box 26)
    - Linde, Hans A., 1967; 1979 (Box 26)
    - Linde, Llewellyn H. (Correctional Assoc.) (Box 26)
    - Livermore, Joseph M. (Asst. Prof.), 1965; 1979 (Box 26)
    - Lockhart, William B. (Dean), 1964-1967; 1969-1970; 1972; 1975; 1980 (Box 26)
    - Loeb, Alan M., 1977; 1980 (Box 26)
    - Loftus, Joseph (New York Times), 1968 (Box 26)
    - Long, Edward V. (Senator), 1965-1967 (Box 26)
    - Lord, John W. (Judge), 1965 (Box 26)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1968-1969; 1973; 1975; 1979 (Box 26)
    - Lothrop, Donald G. (Rev.), 1964 (Box 26)
    - Louisell, David W. (Prof.), 1970; 1975 (Box 26)
    - Love, Jack L., 1970 (Box 26)
    - Lowinger, Paul, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Lusky, Louis, 1966; 1978 (Box 26)
    - Lynch, Jack, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Lynch, Thomas C. (Att. Gen.), 1966; 1968 (Box 26)
    - Lyon, Stewart, 1967 (Box 26)
  - M-R
    - Magbanua, Cornelio C., 1966-1967 (Box 26)
    - Magidson, Adolph, 1966-1969; 1973 (Box 26)
    - Maguire, John M., 1960-1961 (Box 26)
    - Malmquist, Carl P., 1966-1968; 1970; 1980 (Box 26)
    - Mansfield, John H., 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Margoles, Perry Lee, 1961; 1964 (Box 26)
    - Martin, James, 1968-1969 (Box 26)
    - Marshall, J.B. (Dean), 1968 (Box 26)
    - Maryland University, Thomas Cunningham, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Maslow, Will, 1964; 1967 (Box 26)
    - Matish, George G., 1973 (Box 26)
    - Medalie, Richard J., 1966-1968; 1970 (Box 26)
    - Meizlish, Sheldon, 1965-1966; 1968 (Box 26)
    - Meltsner, Michael, 1971-1972 (Box 26)
    - Mendelsohn, Robert I., 1965 (Box 26)
    - Meshbesher, Ronald I., 1965; 1967 (Box 26)
    - Meyerowitz, Sue, 1979 (Box 26)
    - Meyers, Charles, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Microcosmographia Academica, Guide for Academic Politician (Box 27)
    - Miller, Arthur R., 1964-1965; 1968; 1972; 1976; 1980 (Box 27)
    - Miller, Arthur S., 1979 (Box 27)
    - Miller, Charles H., 1966; 1970 (Box 27)
    - Miller, Frank W., 1964 (Box 27)
    - Millstone, Jim (St. Louis Post Dispatch), 1968 (Box 27)
    - Milner, Neal (Grinnell College), 1971 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 27)
    - Modern Criminal Procedure, 1966-1968 (Box 27)
    - Mohammad, Noor, 1971 (Box 27)
    - Mohrenschlager, Helgard, 1970 (Box 27)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1964-1967 (Box 27)
    - Piersante, Vincent W., 1965; 1968; 1971 (Box 27)
    - Pincomb, Ronald A., 1966 (Box 27)
    - Pincus, William (Ford Fdtn.), 1965-1966 (Box 27)
    - Pirsig, Maynard E., 1965; 1973 (Box 27)
    - Pitler, Robert M., 1966-1969; 1971-1973; 1975; 1977-1980 (Box 27)
    - Pitofsky, Robert, 1966; 1969; 1977 (Box 27)
    - Pittendrigh, Colin S. (Prof.), 1967 (Box 27)
    - Plantinga, Olivia L., 1965 (Box 27)
    - Plunkett, Thomas (Prosecuting Attorney), 1971 (Box 27)
    - Pock, John C., 1967 (Box 27)
    - Pollack, Harriet (Prof.), 1969 (Box 27)
    - Pollack, Jack Harrison, 1974-1975 (Box 27)
    - Pollak, Stephen J., 1968 (Box 27)
    - Pomerantz, Mark, 1975 (Box 27)
    - Poole, Cecil F., 1973; 1980 (Box 27)
    - Popa, Robert (Detroit News), 1970 (Box 27)
    - Posner, Richard A., 1974 (Box 27)
    - Poulos, John W., 1973 (Box 27)
    - Powell, Lewis F., Jr. (Justice), 1965; 1972; 1974-1976; 1979-1981 (Box 27)
    - Prentice Hall, Inc., Jeanne Courter, 1971 (Box 27)
    - Price, Ira M. II, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Pringle, Edward E., 1967; 1979-1980 (Box 27)
    - Proffitt, Roy A. (Ass't Dean), 1969 (Box 27)
    - Pryor, Henry T., 1975 (Box 27)
    - Pulaski, Charles A., Jr., 1979 (Box 27)
    - Pye, A. Kenneth, 1965-1966; 1975 (Box 27)
    - Quarles, James C., 1967 (Box 27)
    - Rabinowitz, Jay A. (Chief Justice), 1973 (Box 27)
    - Rahl, James A., 1977 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Paul, 1976 (Box 27)
    - Ranney, James T., 1978; 1980 (Box 27)
    - Ratner, Leonard G. (Prof.), 1971; 2010 (Box 27)
    - Ratushny, Ed, 1970; 1972; 1974 (Box 27)
    - Ravitz, Justen C., 1967; 1968 (Box 27)
    - Read, Frank (Duke University), 1970 (Box 27)
    - Reich, Charles A., 1967 (Box 27)
    - Reichert, Irving, Jr., 1965 (Box 27)
    - Reifsnyder, C. Frank (ABA) (Box 27)
    - Reiser, Stanley, 1974 (Box 27)
    - Reitman, Alan (ACLU), 1964; 1966-1968 (Box 27)
    - Reitze, Arnold W. (Prof.), 1970 (Box 27)
    - Remington, Frank (Prof.), 1959-1964; 1967 (Box 27)
    - Reporter of Decisions, Washington D.C., 1970 (Box 27)
    - Reporters, 1966-1968 (Box 27)
    - Rezneck, Daniel A., 1966-1968; 1972-1973 (Box 27)
    - Rich, Howard I., 1970 (Box 27)
    - Richards, Stephen D. (Minnesota Law Review), 1968 (Box 27)
    - Riesman, David, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Rintala, Barbara V. (UCLA), 1969 (Box 27)
    - Riot Panel, 1967 (Box 27)
    - Ritchie, John, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Roberts, Samuel J., 1965-1966; 1968-1970; 1974; 1977; 1980 (Box 27)
    - Robinson, Cyril D., 1966-1968; 1970; 1972-1973 (Box 27)
    - Robinson, David, Jr., 1965; 1967 (Box 27)
    - Robinson, Paul W., 1967 (Box 27)
    - Robinson, Sophia M., 1965 (Box 27)
    - Robinson, Spottswood W., III, 1967 (Box 27)
    - Rodman, Helgard, 1977 (Box 27)
    - Roediger, Elizabeth, 1967 (Box 27)
    - Rogosheske, Walter F., 1966; 1974 (Box 27)
    - Rosberg, Gerald, 1979 (Box 27)
    - Rose, Jonathan, 1967 (Box 27)
    - Rosen, Sam K., 1965; 1979 (Box 27)
    - Rosenberg, Jay, 1965; 1968 (Box 27)
    - Rosenberg, Maurice, 1968-1969 (Box 27)
    - Rosenbloom, H. David, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Rosenfeld, David, 1970 (Box 27)
    - Rostow, E. V., 1965 (Box 27)
    - Rostow, 1973 (Box 27)
    - Rothblatt, Henry B., 1965-1966; 1980 (Box 27)
    - Rudenstine, Neil F., 1970 (Box 27)
    - Rudolph, Wally, 1979 (Box 27)
    - Ruebhausen, Oscar M., 1966 (Box 27)
    - Ruffin, Roger S. (Hon.), 1968 (Box 27)
    - Runyon, William C., 1967 (Box 27)
    - Ryan, William F., 1970 (Box 27)
  - S-W
    - Salmon, John G., 1971-1975 (Box 27)
    - Sammis, Robert, 1970 (Box 27)
    - Sampson, John J., 1969 (Box 27)
    - Samuels, Gertrude, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Sander, Frank, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Sanders, John L., 1967 (Box 27)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1967 (Box 27)
    - Saunders, George L., Jr., 1968 (Box 27)
    - Savitz, Leonard D., 1965 (Box 27)
    - Sax, Joseph L. (Prof.), 1969-1970 (Box 27)
    - Sayler, Richard H., 1969-1970 (Box 27)
    - Schaefer, Walter V. (Justice), 1964-1969; 1975 (Box 27)
    - Scheuer, James H. (Rep.), 1967 (Box 27)
    - Schiffman, Jacob (Hon.), 1968 (Box 27)
    - Schroeder, Oliver, Jr., 1966 (Box 27)
    - Schultz, Floyd E., 1969 (Box 27)
    - Schwab, Evan L., 1967 (Box 27)
    - Search and Seizure, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Sheridan, Thomas, 1967-1968 (Box 27)
    - Shnayerson, Bob, 1971-1973 (Box 27)
    - Shniderman, Harry L., 1967; 1973; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Siegel, Stanley (Prof.), 1969 (Box 27)
    - Silverglate, Harvey, 1965-1966 (Box 27)
    - Silverstein, Lee, 1964-1965 (Box 27)
    - Simon, Larry, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Sirianni, Stephen J., 1980 (Box 27)
    - Siskind, Paul M. (Dean), 1971 (Box 27)
    - Skardon, James A., 1964-1965 (Box 27)
    - Skolnick, Jerome H., 1966; 1968 (Box 27)
    - Sloane, Joseph (Judge), 1965 (Box 27)
    - Slovenko, Ralph (Prof.), 1966 (Box 27)
    - Smith, Allan F., 1963-1965; 1973 (Box 28)
    - Smith, Raymond C., 1967 (Box 28)
    - Smith, Talbot, 1966; 1976 (Box 28)
    - Sneed, Richard C., 1967 (Box 28)
    - Spearman, Ted, 1969 (Box 28)
    - St. Antoine, Ted (Dean), 1976-1977 (Box 28)
    - Steel, Lewis M. (NAACP), 1968 (Box 28)
    - Stein, Eric (Prof.), 1970 (Box 28)
    - Stein, Robert (Prof.), 1976; 1980 (Box 28)
    - Steinberg, Harris B., 1965-1968 (Box 28)
    - Stern, Carl, 1979 (Box 28)
    - Stern, Herbert (Hon.), 1976 (Box 28)
    - Stevens, John Paul (Justice), 1965-1966; 1979 (Box 28)
    - Stewart, Potter (Justice), 1966; 1969 (Box 28)
    - Stitt, Steven, 1972 (Box 28)
    - Stokes, Louis, 1968 (Box 28)
    - Stone, Christopher D. (Prof.), 1968-1969 (Box 28)
    - Stone, Jerome, 1967; 1972; 1974 (Box 28)
    - Stover, Harney B., Jr., 1965 (Box 28)
    - Strangis, Ralph, 1968 (Box 28)
    - Strassberg, Jay A., 1969 (Box 28)
    - Travel Notes, 1965 (Box 28)
    - Tydings, Joseph D. (Senator), 1968 (Box 28)
    - Uelmen, Gerald (Prof.), 1976 (Box 28)
    - Umin, Steven M., 1970 (Box 28)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1970 (Box 28)
    - University Press of Virginia, 1971 (Box 28)
    - Urban, Otto (Lieutenant), 1967; 1969; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Uviller, H. Richard, 1968-1970 (Box 28)
    - Van Alstyne, William W. (Prof.), 1964; 1966-1967 (Box 28)
    - Vance, Cyrus R. (Hon.), 1968 (Box 28)
    - Vandenberg, Edward L., 1968 (Box 28)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1967 (Box 28)
    - Van Hoomissen, George A., 1971 (Box 28)
    - Van Rooyen, Jan H., 1968 (Box 28)
    - Vera Institute of Justice, 1967 (Box 28)